Hey Jaylen, first off, welcome to
Denver. This is Zach Stevens from from
DNVR. Can you just take us through what
these past 24 hours have been like, how
you found out about the trade and what
it means to be a Bronco?
>> Um, yeah, it's been um exciting. Um,
definitely something new. Um, it was
yesterday morning they gave me the news.
It came out here and then um it's been
great.
>> Parker Gabriel, the Denver Post.
>> Hey Jaylen, welcome to Denver. I'm
curious what you know if you had any
inclination um that that you know is
possible you would be traded and then
also just what your your initial
impressions are of of the Broncos.
Obviously you know Shawn and and Davis
and and and Bo Knicks as a quarterback.
>> Uh yeah, I mean you never know. It's
it's the NFL so you never know what's
for sure and what could happen but um
you know it's uh it's part of the
business and um it's been great. Um my
time here has been great. It feels like
home, feel like family. Everyone's been,
you know, welcoming. So, um, it's been
great.
>> Nick Cosmider, the athletic.
>> Hi, Jaylen. We obviously know you're
you're close with Pastor Tam. What was
that just like between the two of you
getting to kind of experience that
yesterday?
>> Um, it was special. He was one of the
first calls that I made. Um, you know,
we uh talked about this early in our
career. We wanted to get together and
play um with each other. So, just seeing
it happen and um it's special.
Jeff Legwald, ESPN.
>> Jaylen, did did Pat give you any inkling
of what it's like to play here or what
it's like to play for Shawn? Did you get
into any of that with him?
>> Um, not too many details. Um, we kept in
contact um through the years when um,
Coach Payton's been here. So, um, he's
been keeping me in the loop without even
knowing.
>> Eric Dala, Denver Broncos.com.
>> Hey Jaylen, welcome to Denver. just
curious kind of what attributes you feel
like you bring to this wide receiver
room and and how you would describe your
game.
>> Um I think I'm just bringing another
playmaker to the team. Um someone that
can help out and um you know try to make
plays the best of my ability.
>> Mike Cliff 9 News.
>> Yeah. Jaylen, were you aware of um
coming up in trade rumors during the
trade deadline in the middle of the year
um with the Broncos?
Um yeah, a little bit. Um you know, it
was um hearsay, so you never know um
what's true and what's not true. So, uh
you can say I was
>> Andrew Mason, the fan.
>> Hey, Jaylen. Um as you come to Denver,
like what are your personal and teamwide
goals that you want to accomplish now
that you're here?
>> Uh I wouldn't say nothing personal. Um,
I would say for the team, um, just take
it week by week. Um, and you know, try
to go out there and play a good brand of
football and, um, you know, try to stack
some wins together.
>> Troy Rank, the Denver Post.
>> Uh, Jaylen, welcome to Denver. Jaylen,
where does your humility come from? Uh,
sometimes at that position, we don't
necessarily see that. And secondly,
there's so much talk about the chemistry
of this group. How do you think you and
your personality will fit into that type
of environment, that type of locker
room? But where does that humility come
from, Jaylen?
>> Uh, I honestly think it's just the way I
was um brought up. My mom and dad um
obviously try to do a good job as best
they can. Um with um you know, keeping
me um not too high but not too low. Um
so just staying you know, at a a good
head space and I think the it's going to
be a fun group. Um they got a lot of
talent. Court, Marv, Troy, Pat, Little
Jordan. Um, I'm here to help in every,
you know, fashion. Um, making plays um
and, um, learning. I'm excited to learn
from them and them to learn from me. So,
it should be fun. It should be great.
>> Kyle Frederickson, the Gazette.
>> Hey there, Jaylen. I'm curious just what
do you consider your strengths in terms
of versatility uh in terms of able to
being able to play multiple positions at
receiver?
>> Um yeah, I think over my um my my time I
got a chance to play, you know, um all
over the place. So I think that helped
just knowing the offense um inside and
out um being able to put me in in
different spots. So I think that's um
always helpful just being able to go
around and um play different positions.
Arie Stapleton, the Associated Press.
>> Hey Jaylen, welcome to Denver. Um, I was
wondering about your connection with
Rocco, the the cancer fighter, the young
young kid that you developed a
friendship with.
>> Can you just speak to that a little bit?
And do you plan to be, you know,
involved charitywise in in Denver?
>> Uh, I'm definitely going to get in the
community um do something. I know uh PS2
gonna help me um find different things
to get into. um know he do a lot of good
things out here and um Rocco is
definitely someone that's special. Um we
got a special bond. Um and I think
that's just going to continue even you
know where I play at. Um he got you know
family and me on this side. So um it's
honestly great.
>> Darren McKe Altitude.
>> Hey Jaylen, welcome to town. Curious uh
what do you think your role changes as
the number one receiver? And everybody
wants to know, you tan, come on, man.
What's it gonna be in the rings?
>> Uh yeah, man. I don't think it's no uh
number ones. I think everyone's just
here to make plays and and try to win.
Um and that's ultimately the goal for
for the team and u for the organization.
And yeah, I still stand on what I said
about Pat.
>> We have two final questions here. We'll
start with Luca Evans of the Denver
Post, followed by Parker. Go ahead,
Luca.
>> Yeah. Uh Jaylen, welcome to to to
Denver. Just curious, you know, for you
just tracking your career. I mean, 3,000
yard seasons, you know, with with Miami
to start off and then circumstances last
couple years, obviously
organizationally, you know, injuries,
etc. numbers dipped a bit like for you
looking at yourself where you are, do
you feel like this sort of trade
presents kind of a new chance, you know,
a chance at a new chapter for you or at
least a return to the guy that that that
you've been Miami, Bama, etc.
Um, it's definitely new beginnings. Um,
I don't look at it as as that standpoint
of getting back to where I was. I just
look at as new opportunity to go out
there um with a new team that, you know,
um, in a in a great place and, you know,
play along great talent and, you know,
try to help out as best I can.
>> Go ahead, Parker.
>> Yeah, Jaylen, I was just curious,
obviously Denver in the AFC Championship
game last year that close to a Super
Bowl. You've played in a couple playoff
games in your career, but how um
exciting or invigorating is it to be
coming to a team that has been there and
that maybe feels like, you know, you're
one of the pieces that can help them get
to a championship.
>> Um it's exciting, you know, um just
playing, like I said before, just
playing with with great players. Um
everyone been talking about how great
and close the team is, so I'm excited to
be around the guys. um get to know them
and they get to know me and you know um
go from there.
>> Jaylen, that appears to be all the
questions we have for you today. Thank
you so much for taking the time to join
us and welcome to Denver.
>> Thank you so much.